Разрывая землю, пальцы в кровь сотру
Digging up the earth, I'll scrape my fingers bloody.
Леса гробовую тишину прерву
I'll break the forest's deathly silence.
Ветер жутко воет, зов твой мне несёт
The wind howls dreadfully, bearing your call to me.
В этот раз, я верю, точно повезёт
This time, I believe, luck will come for sure.
Не пугайся, милый, суженый родной
Don't be afraid, darling, beloved betrothed.
Жизнь не разлучит нас, не беги, постой!
Life won't part us; don't run— wait!
От меня не скрыться, как и от судьбы
There is no hiding from me, any more than from fate.
Бог услышал с преисподней мои мольбы
God heard my pleas from the underworld.
Чувство, будто снова в груди бьётся сердце
It feels as though a heart beats in my chest again.
Я тебе открою смерти нежной дверцу
I will open the little door to gentle death for you.
Мы покинем мир живых, нам здесь не место
We will leave the world of the living; there is no place for us here.
Ты — живой жених, я — мёртвая невеста
You're a living bridegroom; I'm a dead bride.
Отчего лицо твоё печальное?
Why is your face sad?
Ведь на мне колечко обручальное
After all, I'm wearing a wedding ring.
Может, не по нраву тело бледное
Perhaps the pale body isn't to your liking?
Или ты влюблён во что-то смертное?
Or are you in love with something mortal?
Разве ты не клялся мне в верности и любви
Did you not swear fidelity and love to me?
Пусть мне боль не страшна, и нет во мне живой крови
Though pain doesn't scare me, and there's no living blood in me.
Почему же больно пустоте внутри
Why, then, does the emptiness inside hurt?
Есть во мне остаток горьких слёз, смотри!
There's a remnant of bitter tears in me— look!
Чувство, будто снова в груди рвётся сердце
It feels as though a heart is breaking in my chest again.
Я тебе открою смерти верной дверцу
I will open the little door to certain death for you.
Ты покинешь мир живых, твоё здесь место
You will leave the world of the living; your place is here.
Ты — лишь мой жених, а я — твоя невеста!
You're only my bridegroom, and I'm your bride!
Чувство, будто снова в груди нету сердца
It feels as though there's no heart in my chest again.
Навсегда закрыта моя счастья дверца
My little door to happiness is closed forever.
Я покину мир живых, мне нет здесь места
I will leave the world of the living; there's no place for me here.
Ты — живой жених, я — мёртвая невеста…
You're a living bridegroom; I'm a dead bride…